contactually.com 2019-01-14

# Privacy Policy | Contactually

##### Last updated: May 31, 2018

  * Contactually does not access your contacts for marketing purposes. We also do not sell, give, or trade your contacts to other companies.
  * Some Contactually services are provided in partnership with a third-party. If the third-party is allowed to retain and reuse the information that Contactually sends on your behalf (for example, in contact signature scraping), you may choose whether to use those services by adjusting your Contactually settings. If you do not participate in the service, Contactually will not send data to the service provider on your behalf.
  * Your contacts and activity history are not shared with other Contactually users. One exception may be sharing within your own company/team, based on your settings. If you do not know if your account has been set up to share contacts with others in your company, please ask your team administrator or trainer, or reach out to our Support team at [support@contactually.com](mailto:support@contactually.com) for assistance.
  * Contactually processes the content of the contact communications (e.g. emails, text messages, etc.) to which you have provided us access only to enhance our services for you. Contactually does not market to you or your contacts based on the content of your communications, and we do not share that content.
  * Contactually does not delete or modify your contacts without your permission; we also do not delete or modify your emails, or send emails to your contacts on your behalf, without your permission.
  * You may revoke Contactually’s access to your email account, mobile phone history, and other sources of contacts and activity history at any time; however, revoking access may limit the ability of Contactually to provide services to you.
  * Contactually may track your usage of the platform for the purposes of support, research, product development, or marketing. There are a variety of ways to opt-out of targeted marketing, which are detailed further in this policy.

Our Services enables you to strengthen, track and leverage your contacts and communications with your contacts by using a variety of automated and machine-learning methods to analyze information you have authorized the Services to access (“Content”) in your mobile device, email accounts, and in other online, cloud or mobile services (“Authorized Sources”). This means that Contactually will have access to, and will analyze, among other things, your full emails, contact lists and other materials. All analysis will be conducted consistent with this Privacy Policy, which you should review carefully.

## Our Policy

This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) governs how we collect and process personal information through our websites including www.contactually.com (the “Site”), our customer relationship management applications and related services, and through our normal business activities including when an individual or business registers to use our Services (a “Customer”) or corresponds with us by post, phone, email or otherwise (collectively, the “Services”).

In this Privacy Policy, “Contactually”, “we”, “us”, “our” and other similar references mean Contactually, Inc., a company established in the United States of America with an office at 1200 19th St NW, Ste 210, Washington, DC 20036.

The term “personal information” as used in this Privacy Policy shall mean any information that enables us to identify you, directly or indirectly, by reference to an identifier such as your name, identification number, location data, online identifier or one or more factors specific to you. Personal information excludes anonymous information or information that has had the identity of an individual permanently removed.

By registering for and using the Services, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**

Please note that if you are a user on a team or enterprise account, then, regardless of the representations below, the team or enterprise administrator(s) may have access to your information.

**

## What Information Do We Collect?

### 1\. Information Customers Provide to Us

We collect and store personal information, such as your name, address, email address, phone, usernames and passwords when you register to use our Services, ask a question, complete a form, conduct a transaction, send us an email or attend our events. If you do not provide the requested information, you may not be able to access or use some of the features and functions of our Services.

Furthermore, when you contact us (online or offline) in connection with a request for information or access the Services, we collect personal information necessary to fulfill your request, to grant you access to the Services and to provide you with support. In order to register to use our Services, payment and billing information will also be required and we will maintain purchase records and transactional information which will contain personal information about you and your use of the Services.

### 2\. Information Processed on Behalf Of Our Customers

When Customers use our Services, Contactually will collect personal information and other information (“Content”) relating to third parties contained in mobile devices, email accounts and in other online, cloud or mobile services (“Authorized Sources”) where our Customers have authorized the Services to access such Authorized Sources. using the Services and providing us with access to Authorized Sources, Customers warrant they have the right to provide us with access to each Authorized Sources, as well as to the personal information and Content contained therein.

### 3\. Information We Automatically Collect

We collect content or other information that you may provide or create when you interact with the Services. We may also automatically collect certain usage information when you access our Services, such as Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses, log files, unique device identifiers, pages viewed, browser type, any links you click on to leave or interact with the Services, and other usage information collected from cookies and other tracking technologies (described below). We also collect IP addresses from users when they log into the Services and may also, when you enable location-based Services, collect Global Positioning System (GPS) location data and/or motion data.

We collect general statistics to track user trends for our Services. The information that is collected in this manner does NOT provide us with any personal information about our users, unless combined with other information we hold. This allows us to improve the content and operation of the Services, to determine the most effective ways to communicate with our users and to undertake research and analysis. We also use this technical information to prevent the introduction of viruses and hackers into the Services.

### 4\. Information We Collect From Other Sources

We may also collect information from other companies or third parties or from various service providers to supplement the personal information and Content provided by our Customers to help us maintain the accuracy of personal information and improve our Services.

## How Do We Use Cookies?

Cookies, web beacons and clear gifs are methods used to uniquely identify the device you are using to interact with the Services. We use these technologies to recognize you, optimize the Services for you and to gather information about how users use the Services. Any information provided to third parties through these technologies may provide general information for the enhancement of your user experience by providing more relevant advertising. If you block or refuse these technologies, you may not be able to access or use certain features or functions of our Services and may have a degraded experience. Please see our Cookie Policy for further details.

## How Does Contactually Use Information?

  * To confirm your identity,
  * To complete transactions,
  * To provide, operate and maintain the Services,
  * To operate our business, including internal business intelligence purposes, to conduct research, product development and enhancement,
  * To respond to your requests and deliver the products and services you request,
  * To provide support related to the Services and related customer services,
  * To help us protect our Services, including to combat fraud and protect personal information,
  * To inform you of changes made to our Site and Services,
  * To ensure that our Services are presented most effectively for you and your device;
  * To display content based on your interests;
  * To conduct marketing and commercial activities and to notify you of promotions, updates, or special offers that we think may interest you, in line with your preferences.

## Aggregating and Sharing Combined Information From Many Users

At no time would we aggregate and share information with other users in a manner that would allow you or any other person to be identified.

However, we may prepare and share information about our Customers with third parties, such as advertisers or partners, for research, academic, marketing and/or promotional purposes. For example, we may share demographic data that describes the percentage of our Customers who use mobile services or who use a particular operating system. We or our third party partners may publicly report the aggregated findings of the research or analysis, but only in a way that would not allow you or any other person to be identified.

## Will Contactually Disclose The Information It Collects To Outside Parties?

  * A member of our group or our affiliates,
  * Our professional advisors such as auditors, accountants and lawyers, etc., and
  * Companies that provide services to help us with our business activities, such as data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and payment processing.

We may also disclose personal information and Content if required to do so by law or in good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary (a) to obey the law or comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates; (b) to protect and defend our rights or property or the rights or property of other users of our Service; or (c) to act in an emergency to protect the personal safety of users of our Services or the public.

As Contactually continues to develop its business, we might sell or buy lines of business or assets. If all or substantially all of Contactually’s business (or a line of Contactually’s business) or assets (or the assets of a line of Contactually’s business) are acquired by a third party, personal information will generally be one of the transferred business assets. We reserve the right to include your personal information, collected as an asset, in any such transfer to a third party. If so, you will be provided advance notice of the impending change of control, so that you may have the opportunity to terminate your access to the Service, if necessary.

We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal information and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your personal information for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal information for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

Where personal information relating to European-based individuals is shared with a third party located in a non-EU country that has not received an adequacy decision by the European Commission, we rely on appropriate safeguards, such as the European Commission-approved Standard Contractual Clauses and EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks, to transfer the data.

## Access To Your Authorized Services And CRM.

The primary function of the Services is to receive Access to your Content through your Authorized Services and sync that information to your designated CRM. To do this we must access your Authorized Services with the login information you use to access them. We will request your user name, password, and any other login data that you have set up with your Authorized Sources to enable access. We use this information to update and maintain your Content and to enhance the Services over time.

We also work with other companies or developers to optimize the Services and you may choose to sync, link or connect other third party services, over time. Sometimes we may let you know about another service or product, or another company may let you know about a service or product related to Contactually’s Service. It will be clear who is referring the service or product, and who is providing the service or product. If you choose to accept these services, providing your consent to either the third party or to us, we may exchange your information, including your personal information, as well as information about how you interact with each company's service or product. This exchange of information is necessary to maintain business operations and to provide the ongoing service you've requested. By requesting or accepting these products or services, you are permitting us to provide your information, including your personal information, to the other party.

## What You Can Do to Manage Your Privacy.

You can view and edit your personal information through the Services. You have a choice about the use of information that identifies you, marketing communications you receive from us, and our use of cookies and other tracking technologies.

### i. Updating Your Personal Information.

In connection with your right to manage personal information you provide to us, you may access, update, change, correct or request deletion of your information either through the Services or through our customer support.

### ii. Managing Marketing Communications.

We will honor your choices when it comes to receiving marketing communications from us.

  * Subject to your control, our mobile applications may send push notifications to your mobile device. If you are receiving push notifications and no longer wish to receive these types of communications, you may turn them off at the device level.
  * Remember that even if you choose not to receive marketing communications from us, we will continue to send you mandatory service or transactional communications.

## Social Media Features.

Our Services may use social media features, such as Facebook sharing ("Social Media Features"). These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting within our Services, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Services. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing the relevant Social Media Features.

## What Security Procedures Does Contactually Use To Protect Personal Information And Content?

We use physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to assist us in preventing unauthorized access, maintaining data accuracy, and correctly using your personal information and any Content. We use reasonable efforts to avoid the presence of malware on our Site or as part of the Services. Except to the extent due to our gross negligence or willful misconduct, we expressly disclaim, and you release us from any liability associated with any technical issues caused by the Services, including any malware communicated to your computer or mobile device through any use of the Services. Except as specified in this Privacy Policy, we use commercially reasonable efforts to limit access to your personal information and any Content to the employees, agents, and officers of Contactually who need the information for their jobs.

## External Links

Other companies or organizations may have links to their websites in our Services. We are not responsible for how these other companies or organizations collect, use, disclose, or secure the information that you provide them. If you choose to access a third party website through a link provided as part of our Services, you do so at your own risk and subject to any terms of service or privacy policy (if any) associated with such third party website. Similarly, we use third party-provided APIs and other tools to receive information from accounts to which you give us access (e.g., your email account(s) and your CRM platform). We are not responsible for errors or other issues associated with the functionality of such APIs and other tools.

## Collection Of Information From Children

Contactually does not direct our Services specifically to children. We do not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under thirteen (13). If we learn that a user is under thirteen (13) years of age, we will promptly delete any personal information we have collected about that user. If you are under the age of thirteen (13), please do not send us any information about yourself.

## Consent To Processing In The United States.

Your personal information will be stored in the United States where we are headquartered. We also work with third-party service providers in different countries (for example, we store personal information on Amazon Web Services servers in the United States, we use servers provided by Heroku, a cloud application platform based in the United States, and we have support teams located in the Philippines).

By providing any personal information and/or Content to Contactually, all users, including, without limitation, users in Canada and the member states of the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of such personal information across international borders in accordance with Contactually’s standard operations, including the collection, storage, and processing of such information in the United States of America and the Philippines or other countries in which our employees and contractors may be located.

## How Long Do We Retain Information?

### Information Customers Provide To Us

We will store your personal information, in a form which permits us to identify you for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide the Services. We will retain personal information for a period of 12 months after your account is closed, unless you instruct us to delete the personal information. We will retain and use your personal information after this period as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

### Information Processed On Behalf Of Customers

We will store personal information we process on behalf of our Customers for as long as needed to provide the Services to our Customers. We will retain personal information for a period of 12 months after your account is closed, unless you instruct us to delete the personal information. We will retain and use personal information after this period as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

## Your California Privacy Rights

As stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure — typically by opting in to receive information from a third party that is participating in some activity described in our Services. If you do ask us to share your information with a third party for its marketing purposes, we will only share information in connection with that specific activity, as we do not share information with any third party on a continual basis. To prevent disclosure of your personal information for use in direct marketing by a third party, do not opt in to such use when you provide personal information as part of the Services. Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party’s privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information. 

California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by emailing [CaliforniaPrivacy@Contactually.com](mailto:CaliforniaPrivacy@Contactually.com). Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this email address.

## Your European Privacy Rights

  * We need it to provide the Services under a contract to which you are a party, or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract;
  * It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your rights and interests), such as for research and development, to market and promote the Services and to protect our legal rights and interests;
  * You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose; or
  * We need to process your personal information to comply with a legal obligation.

If you have consented to our use of personal information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time.

We may use your email address to send you newsletter or marketing emails. We will ask for your consent in line with the applicable law when you first provide your personal information. You can opt out by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, or you can contact us on [legal@contactually.com](mailto:legal@contactually.com).

In certain circumstances, you have rights under the GDPR in relation to your personal information. These privacy rights do not apply to Contactually where we process your personal information as a data processor on behalf of our Customers. Where this is the case, any request to exercise your European privacy rights should be directed to our Customer (i.e. the data controller).

### Request access to your personal information.

You may have the right to request access to any personal information we hold about you as well as related information, including the purposes for processing the personal information, the recipients or categories of recipients with whom the personal information has been shared, where possible, the period for which the personal information will be stored, the source of the personal information, and the existence of any automated decision making.

### Request correction of your personal information.

You may have the right to obtain without undue delay the rectification of any inaccurate personal information we hold about you.

### Request erasure of your personal information.

You may have the right to request that personal information held about you is deleted. Request restriction of processing your personal information. You may have the right to prevent or restrict processing of your personal information.

### Request transfer of your personal information.

You may have the right to request transfer of personal information directly to a third party where this is technically feasible.

Where you believe that we have not complied with our obligation under this Privacy Policy or European data protection law, you have the right to make a complaint to an EU Data Protection Authority, such as the UK Information Commissioner’s Office.

## Modification And Notification Of Changes

Contactually may, at our sole discretion, edit this Privacy Policy. Notice of all changes to the Privacy Policy will be provided as discussed in the Terms of Service. You may terminate your access to the Services and your account at any time, also pursuant to the method described in the Terms of Service.

## In Summary

Contactually is committed to protecting your privacy. The information collected from our Services helps us better understand our market and consumer interests. This allows us to serve our customers and business associates with the level of satisfaction they deserve.

If you have questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please send an email message to [legal@contactually.com.](mailto:legal@contactually.com)
